priceisright.com 2019-07-21

# Privacy Policy | The Price is Right

Privacy Policy

FREMANTLEMEDIA NORTH AMERICA, INC.

Effective February 15, 2019

Summary of FremantleMedia North America, Inc. and its affiliates (“FMNA”) Privacy Policy:

1\. **INTRODUCTION** – The Introduction identifies the basic FMNA Services covered by this Privacy Policy and provides a brief overview of what this Privacy Policy covers.

2\. **SUBMISSION AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION** – This section addresses the types of information that FMNA collects directly from users and the collection of non-personally identifiable information via cookies and related technologies by, and on behalf of, FMNA and third parties.

3\. **NOTICE AND CHOICE** – This section provides information on users’ options to control how their information is collected and used, how FMNA notifies users about future Privacy Policy changes, where FMNA stores data, and third party websites that may link to the Services.

4\. **USE AND DISCLOSURE** – This section describes how FMNA uses your information to provide and manage FMNA Services, including when FMNA may disclose your information to third parties that assist FMNA in providing those services.

5\. **SECURITY** – This section describes FMNA‘s security measures.

6\. **USER CONTROL** – This section informs users how to access and change their personal information stored by FMNA, and how to cancel their accounts.

7\. **CONTACT US** – This section instructs users how to contact FMNA.

———————

**1\. INTRODUCTION**  
FremantleMedia North America, Inc., its affiliates and partners (collectively, ” FMNA,” “we” or “us”) provide various entertainment websites including this website (“FMNA Websites”) and related services, such as, applications, community pages and any other features, content, promotions or games offered from time to time by FMNA including when accessed via the Internet, mobile or other devices (collectively, “FMNA Services”). FremantleMedia North America, Inc. is part of the United States based operations of FremantleMedia Group.

As set forth in FMNA Terms of Use, FMNA Services are general audience, are not targeted to children, and

When you submit such information on the Site, you represent that you are at least 18 years of age and that you have the authority to register with the Site. IF YOU ARE UNDER THE AGE OF 18, A PARENT/LEGAL GUARDIAN MUST SUPERVISE YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND REGISTRATION AND BE RESPONSIBLE FOR ALL YOUR CONDUCT ON THE SITE.

This Privacy Policy applies to all users, including both those who use a FMNA Service without being registered with FMNA or subscribing to a FMNA Service and those who have registered with or subscribed to any FMNA Service. This Privacy Policy describes FMNA’s collection and use of users’ personal information (e.g., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name or email address) where that information is not otherwise publicly available on FMNA Services. We also describe generally FMNA’s practices for handling non-personally identifiable information (e.g., interests, demographics and site usage) to the extent such information is associated with a particular user or user account. Your access to and use of certain FMNA Services may require you to accept additional terms and conditions or a privacy policy applicable to such FMNA Services.

This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to us on or through FMNA Services (“ **Unsolicited Submissions** “). Please see our Terms of Use for our policies regarding such Unsolicited Submissions. All such Unsolicited Submissions shall be deemed to be non-confidential, and we shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose and distribute such Unsolicited Submissions to others without limitation, attribution, or compensation.

**2\. SUBMISSION AND COLLECTION OF INFORMATION ON FMNA SERVICES**  
_User Submitted Information_

• **Registration Information** is the information that users must provide to FMNA at registration for a FMNA Service, for example, to receive a newsletter, enter a contest or sweepstakes, play a game or take a survey. Registration Information may include, for example, name, contact information, email address, zip code, birthday and other information you choose to provide us. If you register on a casting site we may request your contact information as well as resume information such as your previous employment or skills. As part of the registration process you may be asked to select a user name and password to be used to access your account and restricted areas of the site.

• **Public Information and Posts** consist of comments or content that you post to FMNA Services and the information about you that accompanies those posts or content, such as a username and/or user picture. Public Information and Posts will always be public which means it will be available to everyone and will be displayed in search results both on FMNA Services and on external search engines.

• **Third Party Information and Content.** If you access a FMNA Service through a third party connection or log-in, your user submitted information may also include your user ID and/or user name associated with that third party service, any information/content you have permitted the third party to share with FMNA, and any information you have made public in connection with that third party service (collectively, “Third Party Information and Content”). Third Party Information and Content obtained in this manner will be governed by this Privacy Policy, any applicable policy of the third party and the terms and conditions and/or terms of use for FMNA Service.

_FMNA Collected Information_

• **Transactional and Site Activity Information**. When users access FMNA Services, we collect certain non-personally identifiable information about those visits. For example, in order to permit your connection to FMNA Services, our servers receive and record information about your computer and browser, including potentially your IP address, browser type, and other software or hardware information. If you access FMNA Services from a mobile or other device, we may collect a unique device identifier assigned to that device or other transactional information for that device in order to serve content to it.

• **Cookies and Similar Technologies**. We may also use cookies and other tracking technologies (such as browser cookies, pixels, beacons, and Adobe flash technology), which are comprised of small bits of data that often include an anonymous unique identifier. Websites send this data to your browser when you first request a web page and then store the data on your computer so the website can access information when you make subsequent requests for pages from that site. These technologies may be used to collect and store information about your usage of FMNA Services, such as pages you have visited, search queries you have run, and advertisements you have seen. FMNA may also use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of FMNA Services to personal information obtained from you or from a reputable third party. For example, if you have asked us to provide you information about our upcoming products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data about your activities on FMNA Websites may allow us to limit the materials we provide you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences. FMNA may use persistent cookies that stay on your browser into the future until they expire or you delete them as well as session cookies that usually are erased when you close your browser window. Further general information about cookies and how they work is available at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

• **Third Party Cookies and Similar Technologies.** Third parties that support FMNA Services by serving advertisements or providing services, such as providing users with the ability to comment on content, allowing users to share content or tracking aggregate site usage statistics may also use cookies or similar technologies to collect similar information. We may allow selected third parties to place cookies through our site to provide us with better insights into the use of the site or user demographics or to provide relevant advertising to you. These third parties may collect information about a consumer’s online activities over time and across different websites when he or she uses our website. FMNA does not control these third party technologies and their use is governed by the privacy policies of these third parties using such technologies. For more information about third party ad networks that use these technologies, see www.aboutads.info.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, but you can change your settings to notify you when a cookie is being set or updated, or to block cookies altogether. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information (e.g., [http://windows.microsoft.com/en- US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-%20US/windows-vista/Block-or-allow-cookies)). Users can manage the use of Flash technologies, including cookies, with the Flash management tools available at Adobe’s website, see <http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security/privacy_policy/faq.html>. Please note that by blocking any or all cookies you may not have access to certain features or personalization available through FMNA Services.

• **Do not Track.** California Business & Professions Code Section 22575(b)(as amended effective January 1, 2014) provides that California residents are entitled to know how FMNA responds to “Do Not Track” browser settings. FMNA does not currently take actions to respond to Do Not Track signals because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a standard once one is created.

• **Third Parties.** To improve the quality of our services, FMNA may supplement the information we collect from you with information we obtain from third parties. If you access a FMNA Service through a third party connection or log-in, we may also collect Third Party Information and Content.

• **Collection of Payment Information by a Third Party.** FMNA uses independent third party service providers to manage sales of FMNA products or services. If you elect to purchase a product or service in connection with FMNA Services you will be required to provide our independent third party service provider with your payment information which may include your credit card information, billing address or other payment information, full name, phone number and shipping address (collectively, “Payment Information”) in order to purchase such product or service. You acknowledge and agree that FMNA does not receive your Payment Information, that this Privacy Policy will not apply to any Payment Information that you provide to any independent third party company on FMNA Services and that all payment obligations related to such purchase shall be governed solely by the applicable independent third party company’s privacy policy. You further acknowledge and agree that FMNA will have no liability for or control over such independent third party company’s use or protection of your Payment Information. You should check the privacy policy of the independent third party company‘s website to determine how it will handle any Payment Information it collects from you and/or processes. You acknowledge and agree that in the event that such independent third party company experiences a data breach that compromises or otherwise affects your Payment Information, FMNA shall in no way be responsible or liable to you for such breach. You should contact the applicable independent third party company regarding any such data breach.

**3\. NOTICE & CHOICE**  
• **Means of Notice and Choice.** This Privacy Policy is the primary means by which FMNA provides you with notice and choice about its collection and use of your personal information. FMNA will not use your personal information in a manner different from what is described in this Privacy Policy without your permission.

• **Privacy Policy Changes.** FMNA may modify this Privacy Policy as necessary. We post the current effective date of this Privacy Policy above. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy that expand our rights to use your personal information, we will notify you to seek your consent either through an email or a prominent posting on FMNA Websites. In the event the last email address you provided to FMNA is not valid or is not capable of delivering the notice to you, FMNA’s dispatch of an email containing the notice to that e-mail address shall nonetheless constitute effective notice. Please check back here from time to time to review any changes.

• **Location of Data.** FMNA Services are hosted in the United States. If you are a user located outside the United States, you understand and consent to having any personal information you provide transferred to, processed, and stored in the United States and other countries where data protection and other privacy laws may not offer the same level of protection as in your jurisdiction, such as in the European Union. This includes the use of cookies and other tracking technologies as described above. As a result, please read this Privacy Policy with care.

• **Linked Services.** FMNA Services may also provide links to sites or services operated by FremantleMedia North America, Inc. affiliates (i.e., that are part of the FremantleMedia Group: “FMNA Affiliated Companies”) or by third parties, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games, rewards programs, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes, or applications developed and maintained by third parties including, any online store. FMNA is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you leave FMNA Services via a link, enable a third party service, or click an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site. Additionally, although all FMNA Affiliated Companies adhere to the FremantleMedia Group corporate Privacy Principles, users who visit a FMNA Affiliated Company site should still refer to its separate privacy policy, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy.

**4\. USE & DISCLOSURE**  
_Information Made Public Through Use of FMNA Services_

Users’ Public Information and Posts are always publicly available to anyone, including other users, search engines, advertisers, third party application developers, and anyone else with access to FMNA Services.

Third Party Information and Content may be publicly available according to the permissions you grant to FMNA, the applicable policies of the third party and the terms and conditions and/or terms of use for FMNA Service.

_FMNA’s Use and Disclosure of Information_

_How we use the information we collect:_  
• **To provide and manage FMNA Services.** We use the information we collect from and about users for our general commercial purposes, such as to provide FMNA Services and features to you, including to measure and improve those services and features, to personalize your experience by delivering relevant content, advertising and marketing messages, to allow you to comment on content, participate in online games, contests, promotions or rewards programs, to enable you to communicate and share with other users or services, and to provide you with customer support and respond to inquiries. We may use aggregated, anonymous data about use of and activity on FMNA Services to assist us in this regard and such data is not subject to this Privacy Policy.

• **To contact you.** FMNA may periodically send promotional materials (e.g., newsletters) or notifications related to FMNA Services to the email address you provided to us at registration or subscription to your account. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials from FMNA, follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. There are certain service notification emails that you may not opt-out of as long as you are registered with or subscribed to FMNA Services, such as notifications of changes to FMNA Services or policies.

• **To deliver relevant advertising.** We may use the information you provide to us, and information we collect about your use of FMNA Services through cookies and other technologies, to assist us in delivering you relevant ads when you visit FMNA Services. We may work with third party advertising networks and advertisers who help deliver these ads to you. We do not share your non-public personal information with these third parties, but we may share anonymized or aggregated information with them to improve the relevancy of the ads you see on FMNA Services. As noted above, these third party advertising networks and advertisers may also use cookies and similar technologies to collect and track non-personally identifiable information such as demographic information, aggregated information, and Internet activity to assist them in delivering advertising that is more relevant to your interests. To find out more about third party online advertising and to opt out of this type of advertising, visit the [Network Advertising Initiative website](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

_Disclosure of Information:_  
We only share your non-public personal information with non-affiliated third parties when we believe sharing is permitted by you or authorized by this Privacy Policy. In addition, FMNA may share your personal information with FMNA Affiliated Companies. We may share your information with unaffiliated third parties as follows:

• **To allow third party service providers to assist us in providing and managing FMNA Services.** FMNA may make your non-public personal information available to certain third party service providers, such as contractors, agents or sponsors, who help us manage or provide FMNA Services by, for example: developing or supporting products and features; conducting email marketing on our behalf; processing payments; administering message boards; fulfilling orders; processing data or statistics; or assisting with the administration, judging and prize fulfillment aspects of contests, promotions and sweepstakes. These outside service providers are required to protect non-public personal information entrusted to them and not use it for any other purpose than the specific service they are providing to FMNA.

• **With your permission or at your request.** We may disclose your information to complete a transaction you have requested, such as to enroll you in a newsletter subscription, enter you in a sweepstakes or to respond to an inquiry or request for information. We may also disclose your information at your request, for example if you request that we share your audition information with our partners or others.

• **To protect the rights of FMNA and our users.** There may be instances when FMNA may disclose user information without providing notice or choice, including situations where FMNA has a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights, property, or safety of FMNA, the FMNA Affiliated Companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of users of FMNA Services or members of the public; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process.

• **To complete a merger or sale of assets.** If FMNA sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, FMNA may transfer your information to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

**5\. SECURITY**  
FMNA uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard user information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. Unfortunately, no transmission of data over the Internet can ever be guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under our control to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal information, FMNA cannot ensure or warrant the security of any personal information you transmit to us. Any such transmission is done at your own risk.

You also play a role in protecting your information. Please safeguard your user name and password and do not share them with others. If we receive instructions using your log-in information we will consider that you have authorized the instructions. If you believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please notify us of the problem by emailing [privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.com](mailto:privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.com).

We are not responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any Public Information and Posts.

**6\. USER CONTROL**  
You may cancel your account by clicking on “delete your account” and may unsubscribe to any FMNA newsletter or promotional email by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of the specific newsletter or e-mail. Remember that even after you cancel your account, copies of some information that is publicly viewable may remain viewable in circumstances where, for example, you have commented on content on FMNA Services or if another person copied, stored or shared your information. We may also retain backup information related to your account on our servers for some time after cancellation for fraud detection or to comply with applicable law or our internal security policies. Unsubscribing from newsletters or promotional emails from us will not stop us from sending you certain service notification emails as you are registered with or subscribed to FMNA Services, such as notifications of changes to FMNA Services or policies.

If you would like to stop receiving messages from us on your mobile phone, please reply to the message with “STOP.” You may also contact your wireless carrier for additional information on receiving or stopping mobile messages.

**Your California Privacy Rights.**  
If you are a California resident, you may request that we not share your personal information on a going- forward basis FMNA affiliates or unaffiliated third parties for their direct marketing purposes by sending an email to [privacy.officer@fremantle.com](mailto:privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.com), with “DISCLOSURE OPT-OUT” in the subject line and your full name, email address, and postal address in the body of the email. We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable.

**7\. CONTACT US**  
If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact FMNA by emailing [privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.com](mailto:privacy.officer@fremantlemedia.com).
